Justin Katic

PROGRAMMER

PORTFOLIO

https://justinkatic.com/

Sydney, NSW

justinkaticdev@gmail.com

in Justin Katic

ABOUT ME

I'm a programmer who specializes in gameplay programming. I'm passionate about programming because I get to learn something new and grow. I enjoy problemsolving and collaborative programming because it challenges me to push my limits. My goal is to work on evolving tech within the industry.

SKILLS

Technologies

- Unity
- Unreal
- Photon networking
- URP

Source Control

- Branching
- Pull requests
- Merging
- Git

Collaboration & Planning

- Sprints
- Standups
- Agile workflow

Languages

- C#
- C++

EXPERIENCE

GAME PROGRAMMER July 2021 - Nov 2021

Dead Bear Studio - Student Project

Steam Link: Demon King Steam

- Integration of network code and ensuring stability.
- Integration and publishing to Steam.
- Worked within Unity engine.
- Collaboration within a team of 7 from Proof of Concept to Gold
- · Identifying and solving bugs.
- Turning a student project into a commercial project.

GAME PROGRAMMER Nov 2020 - May 2021

JEAH! Studio - Student Project

Google Play Link: Lich Legend Android Apple Store Link: Lich Legend IOS

- Operated as a solo programmer working with two artists and a designer.
- Formed a team of four to conceptualize and develop this project to release for IOS and Android.
- Wrote highly maintainable, solid code, forming core framework.
- Implemented and tracked analytic data.
- Worked on as self development task outside of college.

ASSISTANT TEACHER April 2020 - Dec 2021

Academy of Interactive Entertainment

 Assisted faculty by instructing a certificate II class in learning the principles of programming using UE4 Blueprints over 2 weeks.

WAREHOUSE OPERATOR March 2013 - Feb 2021 Aldi

- Communication between team to ensure safe operation of moving equipment to receive and transport items from various warehouse locations.
- Verified accuracy of shipping, receiving documents and maintained records.

EDUCATION HISTORY

Feb 2021 - Dec 2021

Advanced Diploma of Professional Game Development, Specializing in Programming

Academy of Interactive Entertainment

Feb 2020 - Dec 2020

Diploma of Digital and Interactive Games, Specializing in Programming

Academy of Interactive Entertainment

Feb 2017 - Aug 2017

Certificate IV Game Design: Game Design

TAFE NSW - Illawarra